d2jsp.org 2009-04-18

# d2jsp Forums

Privacy Policy

 **INTRODUCTION:**  
We want our users to always be aware of any information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

Website URLs:  

Privacy Policy contact email: [njaguar@d2jsp.org](mailto:njaguar@d2jsp.org?subject=Privacy%20Policy)

 **INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE**  
We respect each site visitor's right to personal privacy. To that end, we collect and use information throughout our website only as disclosed in this Privacy Policy. This statement applies solely to information collected on this website.

The information we collect is:

  * used to improve the content of our Web page.
  * used to notify visitors about updates to our Web site.
  * never shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.

This site collects cookies. ([Cookie Information](http://www.netlingo.com/right.cfm?term=cookies)) In order to view this website, visitors and/or members are not required to complete our registration form. In order to post or contribute to this website, visitors and/or members are required to complete our registration form. During registration a user must give a **valid e-mail address** , but we never sell or give away this information. It is only gathered to contact the user about services on our site for which s/he has expressed interest. Registration is not required to enter our site. We will NOT contact you if you do not indicate that you want contacted. We operate online surveys, and we never sell or share our subscribers' email addresses. This site contains a Private Message system that allows members to communicate with each other. This system is considered private and is not read by anyone but the user. We reserve the right to restrict use of this system to users, and if deemed necessary read posts contained within.

 **NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to: this privacy statement and may not always contact users via e-mail who have indicated to receive such notices.

 **CONFLICT RESOLUTION**  
We are committed to resolving disputes within 24-48 hours. If problems arise, users may contact us by email.

 **CONTACT INFORMATION**  
If site users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: [njaguar@d2jsp.org](mailto:njaguar@d2jsp.org?subject=Privacy%20Policy)

Document Version 1.4
